mycollege.in 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy -Mycollege.in

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully. By using this website of Mycollege.in , you agree to all the conditions in this policy. If you do not agree to all of the conditions contained herein, you may not use this website.

### Information we collect

We collect the IP address and query data from every visitor to the Mycollege.in website. Although we collect query data, we do so for statistical purposes only and do not make any attempt to associate queries with individual visitors. Absolutely no personal data of any kind is collected, extracted, or stored in association with individual search queries, college or school comparison searches, or browsing behavior.

Visitors may also volunteer personal information to Mycollege.in. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Mycollege.in website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this website, other websites, and other forms of media in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

### Transferability of Information

Information collected by Mycollege.in in accordance with this Privacy Policy may be stored and processed within the Democratic Republic of India. By using our website, you consent to any transfer of personal information outside of your country, should we find it necessary.

In the event that we are acquired or merge with another company, or upon a sale of all or portion of our assets, personal information about you will be among the assets transferred to the new company. The new company may handle such information in accordance with its own policies and procedures and not in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Information on this Website

Information on this website may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Information may be changed or updated without notice. We may also make improvements and/or changes in the products and/or the services described in this information at any time without notice.

From time to time, this Privacy Policy may be modified. Updates will be posted in place of this Privacy Policy and will remain accessible to all users of the Mycollege.in website. You agree to this Privacy Policy, and any changes to the same, by visiting this website. For more information please email us [ support@mycollege.in](mailto:%20support@mycollege)

Post Your Answer

Age limit to apply for OICL Recruitment 2015

[Submit](https://www.mycollege.in/discussions/971/.php) Students Discussion Forum
